http://www.nationaldarts.com/category/privacy

(0) Items
View Cart | Total: $0.00 (0)
USD
($)
English
US Dollar (USD)
Euro (EUR)
British Pound (GBP)
Manufacturers
Please Select1 National Darts2 National Darts3 National Darts45American Dart LinesAmeridartsBottelsenDDart TeamDart-StopDartmasterDMIDutchDynaStarGHarrowsLaserMetrolineNodorRuthlessTargetUnicornVoksWinmau
Product Categories
BackboardsCabinetsDart CasesDart FlightsDart MatsDart ScoreboardsDart Sets - Soft TipDart Sets - Steel TipDart ShaftsDart Tips and Add a GramsDartboards - BristleDartboards - ElectronicDarting BooksDarting ClothingDynastar Spin flights & shaftsKits and CombosMiscellaneousNew ProductsOther GamesPins & PatchesSale ItemsSt Paddy's DaySteel Tip BarrelsThrow LinesToolsValentine's Day ProductsClearance & Limited OffersSteel Tip ServiceInformation
Shopping Cart
0 items
Information Pages
PoliciesPrivacyContact Us
Privacy
Privacy Policy
We thank you for visiting our Web site. We want you to feel comfortable about the personal information you may provide to us while transacting business with National Darts Distributors through our Web site. We urge you to read this Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand how we may collect information from you and how that information may be used.  By using our Web site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
The Information We Collect
National Darts Distributors collects personal information on you only in specific circumstances. Personal information is information that can be used to identify you personally. We collect the Personal Information on our on-line registration forms which are accessed using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) to ensure that the data is transferred securely. This information may be used to contact you regarding your account with National Darts Distributors.  You can opt-out from receiving information from National Darts Distributors or request that we delete any personal information we may have collected about you (e-mail address, credit card number, other registration information, etc.) from our database by contacting us directly using any of the following methods:
Contact us via email at: Michel@newbranch.biz
Give us a call at: 888-364-3580
Cookies
National Darts Distributors may also use "cookies" to enable us to store information and prepare customized pages or other personal aspects of the Web site. "Cookies" are small files that we transfer into your computer drive that tells us on an anonymous basis, how often someone visits our site and where they go within our site. You can generally set your browser software to reject cookies.
Children's Privacy
We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. We do not collect Personal Information from anyone who we actually know to be under the age of 13.
Disclosure of Information
Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, or as specifically agreed to by you, we do not share your Personal Information with third parties. There may be instances where we may have to release such Personal Information, however, in order to comply with a valid legal requirement (e.g., a regulation, a search warrant, a court order, etc.), in which case we will notify you unless doing so would violate a law or a court order.
We may disclose Personal Information to our affiliated entities or agents, who will treat the Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Web Site Security
National Darts Distributors wants to ensure that your personal information is kept as secure as possible. If you provide us with personal information or a credit card in order to access secure or premium areas of our site, we will utilize industry standard "Secure Socket Layer" (SSL) encryption. SSL is the most common, and most secure method, of transferring both financial and Personal Information from your Web browser to a remote server.
Updating Your Personal Information
You can always request that we update any Personal Information we may have collected from you. You may contact us directly using any of the following:
Contact us via email at: Michel@newbranch.biz
Give us a call at: 888-364-3580
In the event that we implement significant new uses of the Personal Information, we will notify you and seek your consent prior to implementing such changes. We may also make other changes to this Privacy Policy that will not generally affect our use of your Personal Information. You should check this Privacy Policy regularly for any future changes, and if you don't agree to the revised terms contained in such Privacy Policy, simply exit our Web site immediately.
We thank you for taking the time to review this important information.
Manufacturers
Please Select1 National Darts2 National Darts3 National Darts45American Dart LinesAmeridartsBottelsenDDart TeamDart-StopDartmasterDMIDutchDynaStarGHarrowsLaserMetrolineNodorRuthlessTargetUnicornVoksWinmau
Product Categories
BackboardsCabinetsDart CasesDart FlightsDart MatsDart ScoreboardsDart Sets - Soft TipDart Sets - Steel TipDart ShaftsDart Tips and Add a GramsDartboards - BristleDartboards - ElectronicDarting BooksDarting ClothingDynastar Spin flights & shaftsKits and CombosMiscellaneousNew ProductsOther GamesPins & PatchesSale ItemsSt Paddy's DaySteel Tip BarrelsThrow LinesToolsValentine's Day ProductsClearance & Limited OffersSteel Tip ServiceInformation
Shopping Cart
0 items
Information Pages
PoliciesPrivacyContact Us
Home
Contact Us
Shopping Cart
Checkout
Copyright © 2015 National Darts. All Rights Reserved.
Contact us via email or call toll-free 888-364-3580 Join our email list!
